Angels in the Snow is a drama, family, tv movie
film directed by George Erschbamer.
In Angels in the Snow, the affluent, yet troubled Montgomery family
hits the road for a special Christmas in the mountains.
Judith Montgomery, played by Kristy Swanson.
Charles Montgomery, played by Chris Potter.
Memorial Attendee, played by Carolyn Adair.
Jennifer Montgomery, played by Lizzie Boys.
Joe Tucker, played by Colin Lawrence.
Amy Tucker, played by Catherine Lough Haggquist.
Snow Angels is a 2007 American drama film written and directed by David Gordon Green, based
on Stewart O'Nan's 1994 novel, and starring Sam Rockwell and Kate Beckinsale.
The film is centered on several characters dealing
with loss of innocence in a small town.
It premiered in the dramatic competition at the 2007 Sundance Film Festival, and was
released in the United States on March 7, 2008, by Warner Independent Pictures.
The tone is emotional.